<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="on_boarding_1">1. Welcome to Quokka! Quokka is a personal feeling diary app. You
    can record your feelings alongside their triggers, solutions etc. during your day. Besides, Quokka,
    saving these records for you, it would also try to provide you with solutions based on your needs</string>
    <string name="on_boarding_2">2. The home screen shows the history of what you\'ve felt in the
    last 7 days, you can add feelings by tapping on each card</string>
    <string name="on_boarding_3">3. At the first launch, you won\'t see any data, the app would
    update the home screen automatically, whenever you add a new feeling </string>
    <string name="on_boarding_4">4. You can access the statistics screen by tapping the statistics icon
    to get a general idea of how you\'ve felt in the past </string>
    <string name="on_boarding_5">5. Feelings are complicated, sometimes we cannot clearly
    figure out how we\'re feeling, so here is a cheat sheet for you! tap on any feeling to get a little
    description about it.</string>
    <string name="on_boarding_6">6. Lastly, we value your opinions and ideas very much, if you\'ve got
    anything that you want to tell us, you can send us a mail by using these links</string>

    <string name="contact_us">Contact Us!</string>
    <string name="rate_us">Rate Us!</string>


    <string name="happiness_description">
            Definition: A pleasant emotional state that elicits feelings of joy, contentment and satisfaction
    </string>

    <string name="anxiety_description">
        Definition: A primal emotion that is important to survival and triggers a fight or flight response
    </string>

    <string name="anger_description">
Definition: An emotional state leading to feelings of hostility and frustration
    </string>

    <string name="sadness_description">
Definition: An emotional state characterized by feelings of disappointment, grief or hopelessness
    </string>

    <string name="depression_description">
Definition: Persistent sadness and a lack of interest or pleasure in previously rewarding or enjoyable activities.
    </string>

    <string name="happiness_expression">
            Expressions: Smile, laughter
    </string>

    <string name="anxiety_expression">
         Expressions: Increased heart rate, trouble concentrating,Feeling fatigued often,
        Irritability, Excessive feelings of worry that are difficult to control,
        Difficulty with sleeping
    </string>

    <string name="anger_expression">
 Expressions: Glare, eyebrows drawn together, tight lips
    </string>

    <string name="sadness_expression">
         Expressions: Frown, loss of focus in eyes, tears
    </string>

    <string name="depression_expression">
         Expressions: Feeling suffocated, no eye contact, always feeling tired
    </string>

</resources>